Wishes Can Come True.
Annabelle's Wish is a family, animation, music film directed by Roy Wilson.
Annabelle - a calf who has a special wish for Christmas - wants to be a reindeer
and help Santa Claus drive his sleigh as he delivers his presents!
Annabelle's friends tell her not to get her hopes up, but to everyone's surprise, Santa does indeed meet up
with Annabelle, and the calf gets to help Santa make the holiday special for one young boy.
Adult Billy / Narrator (voice), played by Randy Travis.
Annabelle (voice), played by Kath Soucie.
Child Emily (voice), played by Aria Noelle Curzon.
Grandpa Baker (voice), played by Jerry Van Dyke.
Star (voice), played by Jennifer Darling.
Slim (voice), played by Jerry Houser.
Annabelle's Wish is a 1997 American direct-to-video animated Christmas film that revolves around a young calf who aspires to
fly like one of Santa Claus's reindeer, while forming a friendship with Billy, a young boy who cannot talk.
Narrated by American country singer Randy Travis, it also stars voice actress Kath Soucie as the voice of
Annabelle and also features the voices of Jerry Van Dyke, Jim Varney and Clancy Brown.
Ralph Edwards Films released the film to video on October 21, 1997,
followed by a television broadcast later that year on Fox.
The film explores themes of holiday, reindeer, christmas.